I'll tell you about the things that are being
os comento las cosas que se están
talked about, they are taking
hablando están llevando a médicos
specialist doctors to television and there are
especialistas a la televisión y hay
some theories, two in particular and it is
algunas teorías dos en concreto y que
very likely that one of them is the
muy probablemente sea una de ellas los
signs on the 28th,
indicios día 28 se ingresa la la
Princess K Middleton is admitted, okay, she is suddenly admitted
princesa K middleton vale se ingresa de
urgently, let's say it is
repente de manera urgente digamos que es
something, a pain or something that comes on
algo un dolor o algo que le entra de
suddenly, in less than a month she is undergoing
repente en menos de un mes está operando
an operation that takes many hours and they
una operación de muchas horas y
rule out that it is aesthetic, there is talk of
descartan que sea estético se habla de
diverticulitis, let's see, diverticula,
diverticulitis a ver divertículos
almost all of us have diverticula, unless you lead
tenemos casi todos a no ser que lleves
a perfect life, you have diverticula,
una vida perfecta divertículos tienes
they are like little bags, I
los divertículos son como unas bolsitas
'm going to call it that, so they form at the
voy a llamarlo Así que se forman al
end of the colon and then the other thing they are
final del colon y luego de la otra cosa
talking about is very strong
que hablan es muy fuerte